<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SNLab</title>
    <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on SNLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powered by [Hugo](//gohugo.io). Theme by [cooler](https://gitlab.com/snlab-freedom/hugo-theme-cooler).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://snlab-freedom.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>ARO Workshop on Software Defined Networking for Army Applications</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-06-14-aro-workshop-on-software-defined-networking-for-army-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-06-14-aro-workshop-on-software-defined-networking-for-army-applications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNLab organized the workshop in May 5-6&lt;sup&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &#39;Times New Roman&#39;;font-size: 16px;vertical-align: super&#34;&gt;th&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, 2016. This workshop bring together experts from software-defined networking, wireless/hybrid networks, tactical networks, high-performance computing and related disciplines to investigate both the benefits and the issues when applying SDN to army applications. The emergence of SDN, whose key features include separation between the data-plane and the control-plane of networks, and logically centralized network control, has potential to completely reshape the field of computer networking. Going beyond conceptual models, the existing deployment of SDN in major data centers (e.g., Google and Microsoft data centers) has demonstrated the substantial gain and flexibility of SDN. However, the existing initiatives of SDN focus mostly on non-tactical data center networks, service provider networks, and enterprise networks. Given the substantial potential of SDN, it is imperative that we develop a better understanding of both the impacts and the potential issues of applying SDN to Army Applications, primarily for multi-hop wireless/hybrid networks, but also for high performance computing in the army context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We invited some famous professors and scientists to discuss some SDN challenge problem, including Yale, UCLA, Imperial College, University of Pennsylvania, Caltech, Carnegie Mellon University, Princeton University, MIT, DARPA, IBM, Uber etc. famous university and company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Y. Richard Yang as a chair , made a key note speech. And he introduced some recently research. A key benefit of SDN is logically centralized control. There is a large body of existing work of SDN control path, but they are mostly in the context of wired networks such as data center networks and wide-area networks (WAN). By control path, we mean the complete spectrum from controller placement, controller fault tolerance, controller programming, and controller-forwarding elements integration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This workshop reviewed key related work and warmly discussed issues with potential outcomes. The workshop successful hold and all of attendees are very satisfied with the outcome of the workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNlab Members attended the NSF Workshop on Algorithms for Software-Defined Networking</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-06-14-snlab-members-attended-the-nsf-workshop-on-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-06-14-snlab-members-attended-the-nsf-workshop-on-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNLab members (Hu Ning, Du Haizhou, Xiang Qiao, Pen Dan) recently attended the NSF Algorithms in the Field (AiTF) Workshop on Algorithms for Software-Defined Networking in June 2-3, 2016. This workshop is sponsored by the Algorithms in the Field (AiTF) program of the National Science Foundation and the DIMACS(Center for Discrete Mathematics &amp;amp; Theroetical Computer Science Technology Center). Including UC Berkeley, Stanford, Carnegie Mellon University, Princeton University, MIT, Google, Microsoft attended the workshop, and discuss together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main goal of this workshop is to bring together researchers working at the intersection of the theory and practice of networking, with a special focus on the applicability of these ideas to SDN, in the hope of jumpstarting collaborations between theoreticians and networking researchers in this area. This provide not only an opportunity for the networking community to get new ideas and approaches, but will also provide a tremendous opportunity for the theoretical community, both as a source of new algorithmic problems and as a way to have a direct impact. This is to some extent in contrast to the traditional networking paradigm, where the algorithmic problems often do not have a path to deployment as they are constrained by existing protocols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://snlab-freedom.github.io/images/posts/2016-06-14-snlab-members-attended-the-nsf-workshop-on-algorithms.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width:40%&#34; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xiang Qiao, represented the SNLab made a speech about Magellan: Toward Automatic Multi-Table SDN Programming. He systematic tell that Multi-table pipelining has emerged as a key technique for the next-generation SDN data path. Programming such a data path model, however, can be challenging. In this talk, he also discusses several algorithmic challenges in programming multi-table pipelines. This talk attracted both academic and industrial researchers. They gave some good suggestion and comments to us. And most of them highly agree with our research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this workshop, we discussed with the workshop attendees on the most important algorithmic problems involving SDN. This serves as a central point of reference for future work in algorithms for SDN, and hopefully spur further research in the way that lists of open problems have led to further research in other parts of algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Yang: SDN programming automation: abstraction, tools, and implementations</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-06-13-sdn-programming-automation-abstraction-tools-and-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-06-13-sdn-programming-automation-abstraction-tools-and-applications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June 1 to 2, 2016, “Global SDNFV Tech Conference 2016” has been grandly held in Beijing. Prof. Yang and SNLab members are invited to participate in this conference. Prof. Yang made a speech entitled “*SDN programming automation: abstraction, tools, and implementations*”. In this talk, Prof.Yang explained the goal of SNLab, cache and acceleration automation, and present some prototypes of our projects, which include &lt;em&gt;Magellan&lt;/em&gt;, automatic generation of multi-level flow tables, &lt;em&gt;Maple&lt;/em&gt;, using TraceTree to change high level algorithm policies into the low level flow entries, and &lt;em&gt;FAST&lt;/em&gt;, automatic re-execution function instances to make sure the correctness of user functions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demonstration of ALTO SPCE on 2016 Internet2 Global Summit</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-05-31-demonstration-of-alto-spec-on-2016-internet2-global-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-05-31-demonstration-of-alto-spec-on-2016-internet2-global-summit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2016 Internet2 Global Summit&lt;/em&gt; was successfully held in Chicago, Illinois on May 15 to May 18.The Internet2 Global Summit is a leading forum to support and drive the advancement of research and education, spur next-generation innovation and accelerate global discovery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNlab cooperated with CERN from Caltech on the discussion and demonstration of latest achievements among this summit. Core members including Jensen Zhang, Mingming Chen, Qiao Xiang, Kai Gao, May Wang and Shawn Lin attended the summit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Achievements on development of ALTO SPCE was presented and received great acclaim from attendees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://snlab-freedom.github.io/images/posts/2016-05-31-demonstration-of-alto-spec-on-2016-internet2-global-summit-1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNlab&amp;rsquo;s major work is based on the SDN controller OpenDaylight. This demonstration is bulit on the environment provided by Caltech, with several Pica8 and SDN switches(from Dell) and work with standard protocol OpenFlow to connect OpenDaylight. The convertion from virtual environment to the real is a great breakthrough .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://snlab-freedom.github.io/images/posts/2016-05-31-demonstration-of-alto-spec-on-2016-internet2-global-summit-2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNlab and Caltech will keep working  together on the great issues of SDN.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Summit of SNLab held</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-05-31-spring-summit-of-snlab-held/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/posts/2016-05-31-spring-summit-of-snlab-held/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spring Summit of SNlab is held on March 21 to March 23 in College of Computer Science , Tongji University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summit invited researchers from Qinghua, Yale, University of Science and Technology, Shanghai Jiao Tong University, Nanjing University of Posts and telecommunications and Chinese Academy of Sciences to engage in the summit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/about</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/about</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Postdoc Positions at SNLab at Tongji-Yale Center of Advanced Networks and Networked Systems
Founded by Professor Y. Richard Yang &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cs.yale.edu/homes/yry/&#34;&gt;http://www.cs.yale.edu/homes/yry/&lt;/a&gt; in the summer of 2014, and hosted in the Institute of Advanced Studies at Tongji University, the Systems Networking Lab (SNLab) will provide astimulating, world-class environment for the advancement of both theory and systems of networks and networked systems.
With continued development and wide deployment of advanced, transformative networks and systems techniques, such as software defined networks, Internet of things, 5G networks, mobile networks, network function virtualization, and Cloud computing, networks and networked systems remain an exciting, dynamic field that new ideas continue to emerge and new systems continue to be developed and deployed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prof. Y. Richard Yang（杨阳）&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;tbody style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box;&#34;&gt;&lt;tr class=&#34;firstRow&#34; style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box;&#34;&gt;&lt;td valign=&#34;top&#34; style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box; padding: 0px; border: 1px solid rgb(221, 221, 221);&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://snlab-freedom.github.io/images/about/picture1_yy.png&#34; title=&#34;Yang Richard Yang&#34; alt=&#34;Yang Richard Yang&#34; style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box; border: 0px; vertical-align: middle;&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign=&#34;top&#34; style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box; padding: 0px; word-break: break-all; border: 1px solid rgb(221, 221, 221);&#34;&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box; margin-bottom: 10px;&#34;&gt;美国耶鲁大学终身正教授及同济大学教授。主要从事下一代互联网体系结构、SDN编程、互联网内容分发、网络流量优化和云计算等领域的研究。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box; margin-bottom: 10px;&#34;&gt;&lt;br style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;box-sizing: border-box; margin-bottom: 10px;&#34;&gt;报告题目：SDN概述&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Y. Richard Yang is a Professor of Computer Science at Yale, where he founded and leads the Laboratory of Networked Systems (LANS). He is also a professor at Tongji University, where he leads the SNLab. Prof. Yang&amp;rsquo;s current research focus is on new computer network architectures, SDN programming, content distribution networks, and network-application interactions. He has published more than 10 papers in ACM SIGCOMM, the flagship conference on networking; among which 4 were nominated as best papers. His team proposed the framework of P4P for network-application interactions, which is adopted by IETF by forming the ALTO Working Group, which has defined the ALTO Protocol. His work has been implemented/adopted in products/systems of major companies (e.g., AT&amp;amp;T, Alcatel-Lucent, Cisco, Microsoft, PPLive, Youku), and featured in mainstream media including Economist, Forbes, Guardian, Chronicle of Higher Education, Information Week, MIT Technology Review, Science Daily, USA Today, Washington Post, and Wired, among others. His awards include a CAREER Award from the National Science Foundation and a Schlumberger Foundation Award. Dr. Yang&amp;rsquo;s received his B.E. degree in Computer Science and Technology from Tsinghua University (1993), and his M.S. and Ph.D. degrees in Computer Science from the University of Texas at Austin (1998 and 2001).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://snlab-freedom.github.io/images/about/picture2_yy.png&#34; style=&#34;width: 142px&#34; title=&#34;Yang Richard Yang&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biography:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard Yang is a Professor of Computer Science at Yale, where he founded and leads the Laboratory of Networked Systems (LANS). He is also a professor at Tongji University, where he leads the SNLab. Prof. Yang’s current research focus is on new computer network architectures, SDN programming, content distribution networks, and network-application interactions. He has published more than 10 papers in ACM SIGCOMM, the flagship conference on networking; among which 4 were nominated as best papers. His team proposed the framework of P4P for network-application interactions, which is adopted by IETF by forming the ALTO Working Group, which has defined the ALTO Protocol. His work has been implemented/adopted in products/systems of major companies (e.g., AT&amp;amp;T, Alcatel-Lucent, Cisco, Microsoft, PPLive, Youku), and featured in mainstream media including Economist, Forbes, Guardian, Chronicle of Higher Education, Information Week, MIT Technology Review, Science Daily, USA Today, Washington Post, and Wired, among others. His awards include a CAREER Award from the National Science Foundation and a Schlumberger Foundation Award. Dr. Yang’s received his B.E. degree in Computer Science and Technology from Tsinghua University (1993), and his M.S. and Ph.D. degrees in Computer Science from the University of Texas at Austin (1998 and 2001).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;杨阳，博士，2014 年第十批中国千人计划国家特聘专家, 现为耶鲁大学终身正教授，同济大学计算机系教授、博士生导师。1993 年获得清华大学计算机工程与技术学士学位，1998 和2001 分别从美国Austin 大学获得硕士和博士学位。主要从事下一代互联网体系结构、SDN 编程、互联网内容分发、网络流量优化和云计算等领域的研究。他曾担任耶鲁大网络系统实验主任，他先后获得美国国家科学基金会National Science Foundation 和Schlumberger Foundation 基金奖。他一直坚持理论研究，国际标准，与实际系统相结合的学术风格。从2001年至今在国际计算机网络领域最具影响力的国际顶级会议ACMSIGCOMM上发表论文11 篇，其中4 篇获SIGCOMM最优论文提名，始终位于全球前列; 他的团队提出的P4P 概念被国际互联网标准组织(IETF)采用并成立IETF ALTO 工作组，成为互联网标准ALTO 协议的基础；他所领导的Maple SDN 编程语言获ACM SIGCOMM 2013最优论文提名，2014 Google 研究奖励（2014 Google Faculty Research Award)， 及美国国家自然基金（NSF）部署支持（2014 NSF CCIIE Award）; 他的团队所设计的多个网络系统与算法在商业系统（如思科，阿朗，谷歌，微软，百度，Youku 等的产品）中实现并部署; 他的研究被主流媒体如Economist, Forbes, Guardian, Chronicle of Higher Education, Information Week, MIT Technology Review, Science Daily, USA Today, Washington Post, and Wired 等报道。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haizhou Du</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/haizhou_du/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/haizhou_du/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;haizhou-du&#34;&gt;Haizhou Du&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:duhaizhou@gmail.com&#34;&gt;duhaizhou@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jensen Zhang</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/jensen_zhang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/jensen_zhang/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;jensen-zhang&#34;&gt;Jensen Zhang&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jingxuan.n.zhang@gmail.com&#34;&gt;jingxuan.n.zhang@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kai Gao</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/kai_gao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/kai_gao/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;kai-gao&#34;&gt;Kai Gao&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:godrickk@gmail.com&#34;&gt;godrickk@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May Wang</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/may_wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/may_wang/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;may-wang&#34;&gt;May Wang&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:whr_hr_r@163.com&#34;&gt;whr_hr_r@163.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiao Xiang</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/qiao_xiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/qiao_xiang/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;qiao-xiang&#34;&gt;Qiao Xiang&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:xiangq27@gmail.com&#34;&gt;xiangq27@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shawn Lin</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/shawn_lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/shawn_lin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;shawn-lin&#34;&gt;Shawn Lin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:linxiao9292@outlook.com&#34;&gt;linxiao9292@outlook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sheldon Shen</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/sheldon_shen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/sheldon_shen/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;may-wang&#34;&gt;May Wang&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:shenxvdong1@gmail.com&#34;&gt;shenxvdong1@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shenshen Chen</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/shenshen_chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/shenshen_chen/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;shenshen-chen&#34;&gt;Shenshen Chen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:cs90911@gmail.com&#34;&gt;cs90911@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Wang</title>
      <link>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/tony_wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snlab-freedom.github.io/members/tony_wang/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tony-wang&#34;&gt;Tony Wang&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:xinwang2014@hotmail.com&#34;&gt;xinwang2014@hotmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>